<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on Simple Lookups</title><link>/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Simple Lookups</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 10:54:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Site Updates</title><link>/2020/02/site-updates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 10:54:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>/2020/02/site-updates/</guid><description>Over the past few days, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on giving SimpleLookups an actual website, instead of just having the site redirect to my blog. As of today, the new site is live, and I&amp;rsquo;ve moved the documentation and release announcements from my blog to this site. My blog is still available at russellwritescode.com if you&amp;rsquo;re interested (you&amp;rsquo;ll notice both sites use the same theme).
Speaking of documentation - the old documentation was pretty barebones and was missing a number of things, so I reorganized it and added several more pages worth to help people who would implement SimpleLookups.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 2.0.1 Released</title><link>/2016/05/simplelookups-2-0-1-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 20:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2016/05/simplelookups-2-0-1-released/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v2.0.1. This version includes the following changes:
Some code cleanup and consistency updates. Added unit tests to public source code repository. Added script to stage a testing environment using SQL Server LocalDB. Version 2.0.1 is now available on NuGet and on this site. Please install using Visual Studio, if possible. This way, your download counts!</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 2.0 Released</title><link>/2015/08/simplelookups-2-0-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 20:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2015/08/simplelookups-2-0-released/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v2.0. This version includes the following changes:
New Features:
Lookup Caching (Enabled by Default) Core improvements/optimizations. Support for .NET 4.5.1, 4.5.2, and 4.6. Removed Features:
Support .NET 2.0 and 3.0. Version 2.0 is now available on NuGet and on this site. Please install using Visual Studio, if possible. This way, your download counts!</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 2.0 Beta 1</title><link>/2015/08/simplelookups-2-0-beta-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 04:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2015/08/simplelookups-2-0-beta-1/</guid><description>Today, I&amp;rsquo;m releasing the first beta of SimpleLookups v2.0. This version includes the following changes:
New Features:
Lookup Caching Core improvements/optimizations. Support for .NET 4.5.1, 4.5.2, and 4.6. Removed Features:
The final version will not support .NET 2.0 and 3.0. Caching is enabled by default. You can turn it off by adding the following attribute to the node in your web.config: enableCaching=&amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo;. Or, if you use the SimpleLookups.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 1.6 Released</title><link>/2014/06/simplelookups-1-6-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 20:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2014/06/simplelookups-1-6-released/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v1.6.0. This version includes the following changes:
New Features:
Specify column suffixes for Name/Description/Code/Id columns. Specify column name of Active column. Specify whether or not to prepend the table name to the column names. Core improvements/optimizations. Version 1.6 is now available on NuGet and on this site. I recommend NuGet, but to each their own.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 1.5.1 Released</title><link>/2014/01/simplelookups-1-5-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 02:17:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2014/01/simplelookups-1-5-1-released/</guid><description>Today, I&amp;rsquo;m releasing SimpleLookups 1.5.1.
This version is a major rewrite of a lot of the core stuff, so it contains no API changes. Basically, if you used it before, it should still work great for you today. The only new thing is that you can now configure it through the app.config/web.config files. The download package contains an example of how to do that, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be updating the documentation so that it&amp;rsquo;s even more clear.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 1.2 Released</title><link>/2013/12/simplelookups-1-2-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2013/12/simplelookups-1-2-released/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v1.2. This version includes the following changes:
New Features:
Get a list of lookup values based on a code or a list of codes. Remove a list of lookup values based on a code or a list of codes. Changed Features:
The methods &amp;ldquo;GetActive&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;GetAll&amp;rdquo; are deprecated and are replaced by a single method called &amp;ldquo;Get&amp;rdquo;. An activeOnly flag is passed in to the method.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 1.1 Released</title><link>/2013/12/simplelookups-1-1-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 01:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2013/12/simplelookups-1-1-released/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v1.1, which is a small change to the library that is taking the world by storm. (Disclaimer: May not be as popular as advertised.)
This version includes a couple of small API changes, as well as a couple new methods.
New Features:
Get a list of lookup values based on a list of ids. Remove a list of lookup values based on a list of ids.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups 1.0 Released</title><link>/2013/12/simplelookups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 21:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2013/12/simplelookups/</guid><description>Today, I released SimpleLookups v1.0, which is a project that I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to release for a long time. This is a small .NET 2.0+ library that is designed to make &amp;ldquo;lookup&amp;rdquo; values easy to retrieve from a SQL Server database.</description></item></channel></rss>