<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classes on Simple Lookups</title><link>/classes/</link><description>Recent content in Classes on Simple Lookups</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:47:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/classes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lookup Class</title><link>/classes/lookup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/classes/lookup/</guid><description>Abstract class with a base implementation of ILookup.
Namespace Import using SimpleLookups; Jump To Id Name Description Code Active Id A unique id associated with the lookup value. This is how the value should be referenced in other tables.
Signature int Id { get; set; } Available 1.0+
Name The name of the lookup value.
Signature string Name { get; set; } Available 1.</description></item><item><title>LookupManager Class</title><link>/classes/lookupmanager/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 23:34:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>/classes/lookupmanager/</guid><description>Manages a single lookup type.
Namespace Import using SimpleLookups; Jump To Constructor Create Get (int) Get (IList&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;) Get (string) Get (IList&amp;lt;string&amp;gt;) Get (bool) Update Delete (int) Delete (IList&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;) Delete (string) Delete (IList&amp;lt;string&amp;gt;) Deprecated and Removed Methods GetById GetAll GetActive Constructor Creates a new instance of LookupManager to manage lookups of type T. T must implement SimpleLookups.Interfaces.ILookup somewhere in it&amp;rsquo;s inheritance chain, or inherit from SimpleLookups.</description></item><item><title>SimpleLookups Class</title><link>/classes/simplelookups/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 23:32:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/classes/simplelookups/</guid><description>This is the main static class of the SimpleLookups package.
Namespace Import using SimpleLookups; Jump To Initialize (string) Initialize (string, bool, int) Initialize (string, string, string, string, string, string, bool) Initialize (string, string, string, string, string, string, bool, bool, int) AddConnectionString Initialize (string) Initializes SimpleLookups with the default connection string.
Signature static void Initialize( string defaultConnectionString ); Available 1.0+
Initialize (string, bool, int) Initializes SimpleLookups with the default connection string, and the provided cache settings.</description></item></channel></rss>